<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Charles Geng's Web</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Charles Geng's Web</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 16:52:18 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://charlesgeng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pro React 16 - Part 3</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/proreact16-part3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 16:52:18 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/proreact16-part3/</guid><description>Chapter 18 CREATING COMPLETE APPLICATIONS Updating an object with setState in React. link
Array.prototype.concat()
Syntaxlink concat() concat(value0) concat(value0, value1) concat(value0, value1, ... , valueN) Chapter 19 USING A REDUX DATA STORE Name Description action An action describes an operation that will change the data in the store. Redux doesn’t allow data to be modified directly and requires actions to specify changes.</description></item><item><title>The Road To Learn React</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/theroadtolearnreact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 14:05:40 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/theroadtolearnreact/</guid><description>Hoisting Before the declaration of the function or variables, you can use them. Only declarations are hoisted, without initialize. Initializations using let and const are also not hoisted. // The program can be excuted without any errors. console.log(num); //output undefined num = 7; var num; Scoping let and const are block-scoped in JS, in contrast to var, which is function-scoped. Const vs Let A variable declared with const cannot be re-assigned.</description></item><item><title>为你，千千万万遍 -- 《追风筝的人》</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/%E8%BF%BD%E9%A3%8E%E7%AD%9D%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%BA/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 16:03:20 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/%E8%BF%BD%E9%A3%8E%E7%AD%9D%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%BA/</guid><description>昨晚终于把《追风筝的人》看完了，这也是第一次体会到阅读的快意，不惑之年才体会到读小说的快乐，或许是有点儿晚了，不过迟到总比没到好。
还记得那天清晨，一个人窝坐在沙发上，妻儿们正睡得香甜，看着书中的人物在与命运抗争的时候，多多少少也为自己的命运感到庆幸。任何一个普通人如果出生在那样的环境中，都很难改变自己的命运。活着是一种奢望，死亡才是最好的归宿。
“为你，千千万万遍”这句话贯穿小说始终的话，我想它不只是哈桑对阿米尔表达的忠诚，也是每个阿富汗人民想对他们深爱的那片土地所说的话。当一个生活富足的父亲由于战争不得不带着自己的儿子远走他乡时，他能带走的只有对那片深受着的土地的思念。
在读这部小说之前，提到阿富汗这个国家，我的脑海中浮现的名词只有：“战争”，“贫穷”，“恐怖主义”和“塔利班”。阿富汗并非自始至终就是这个样子的，上世纪70年代初，阿富汗还是一个祥和安宁的国家，但是随着政权的倒台，以及随后爆发的苏阿战争，将这个国家彻底地拉入了痛苦的深渊。如果说这部小说让我学到了什么，那就是一定不要避免战争的爆发。</description></item><item><title>React Self Study</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/proreact16-part2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 10:23:53 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/proreact16-part2/</guid><description>Book Pro React 16 ISBN: 978-1-4842-4450-0 homepage TODO LIST TODO: Chapter 13. Know more about componentWillUnmount. How to close network connections, how to stop any asynchronous tasks. Chapter 09 to be updated Chapter 10 to be updated Chapter 11 Stateful Component Stateful Component Definition import React, { Component } from &amp;#39;react&amp;#39; export default class statefulComponent extends Component { constructor(props) { super(props) this.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/about/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 13:10:52 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/about/about/</guid><description>Hi There. I am Charles, 耿 琪 in Chinese I am a software developer from China Currently, I am living in Japan with my family You can find me in LinkedIn, Github or LeetCode</description></item><item><title>How to Setup My Personal Blog With Hugo, Github</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/how-to-setup-my-personal-blog-with-hugo-github/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 10:33:24 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/how-to-setup-my-personal-blog-with-hugo-github/</guid><description>Install Hugo on your PC Nothing special, just follow the instructions of official documentation Here
Create a repository in github Create a repository with &amp;lt;yourname&amp;gt;.github.io Create the new site Use hugo command to generate the new site hugo new site charlesgeng.github.io Checkout the repository from github git init git remote add origin https://github.com/CharlesGeng/charlesgeng.github.io.git git fetch git checkout origin/master -ft Add mainroad theme to the site.</description></item></channel></rss>