<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT on Charles Geng's Web</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/categories/it/</link><description>Recent content in IT on Charles Geng's Web</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 14:05:40 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://charlesgeng.github.io/categories/it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Road To Learn React</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/theroadtolearnreact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 14:05:40 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/theroadtolearnreact/</guid><description>Hoisting Before the declaration of the function or variables, you can use them. Only declarations are hoisted, without initialize. Initializations using let and const are also not hoisted. // The program can be excuted without any errors. console.log(num); //output undefined num = 7; var num; Scoping let and const are block-scoped in JS, in contrast to var, which is function-scoped. Const vs Let A variable declared with const cannot be re-assigned.</description></item><item><title>React Self Study</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/proreact16-part2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 10:23:53 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/proreact16-part2/</guid><description>Book Pro React 16 ISBN: 978-1-4842-4450-0 homepage TODO LIST TODO: Chapter 13. Know more about componentWillUnmount. How to close network connections, how to stop any asynchronous tasks. Chapter 09 to be updated Chapter 10 to be updated Chapter 11 Stateful Component Stateful Component Definition import React, { Component } from &amp;#39;react&amp;#39; export default class statefulComponent extends Component { constructor(props) { super(props) this.</description></item><item><title>How to Setup My Personal Blog With Hugo, Github</title><link>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/how-to-setup-my-personal-blog-with-hugo-github/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 10:33:24 +0900</pubDate><guid>http://charlesgeng.github.io/post/how-to-setup-my-personal-blog-with-hugo-github/</guid><description>Install Hugo on your PC Nothing special, just follow the instructions of official documentation Here
Create a repository in github Create a repository with &amp;lt;yourname&amp;gt;.github.io Create the new site Use hugo command to generate the new site hugo new site charlesgeng.github.io Checkout the repository from github git init git remote add origin https://github.com/CharlesGeng/charlesgeng.github.io.git git fetch git checkout origin/master -ft Add mainroad theme to the site.</description></item></channel></rss>